<odoo>
    <!--    Author-->
    <record id="andrzej_sapkowski_id" model="author.of.book">
        <field name="name">Andrzej</field>
        <field name="last_name">Sapkowski</field>
        <field name="biography_text">
            He is a Polish fantasy writer. He is best known for his book
            series The Witcher, which has been translated into 37 languages
            making him the second most-translated Polish science fiction
            and fantasy writer after Stanisław Lem. His books sold over
            15 million copies. He is the recipient of the David Gemmell
            Award and the World Fantasy Life Achievement Award.
        </field>
    </record>

    <record id="tolkien_id" model="author.of.book">
        <field name="name">John Ronald Reuel</field>
        <field name="last_name">Tolkien</field>
        <field name="biography_text">
            Tolkien 3 January
            1892 – 2 September 1973) was an English writer, poet,
            philologist, and academic, best known as the author of the high
            fantasy works The Hobbit and The Lord of the Rings.
        </field>
    </record>

    <!--    Book-->

    <record id="sword_of_destiny_id" model="library.book">
        <field name="name">Sword of Destiny</field>
        <field name="book_description">
            Sword of Destiny (Polish: Miecz przeznaczenia) is the first
            published (in Polish) of the two collections of short stories
            (the other being The Last Wish), both preceding the main
            Witcher Saga. The stories were written by Polish fantasy
            author Andrzej Sapkowski. The first Polish edition was
            published in 1992; the English edition was published in the
            UK by Gollancz in 2015.
        </field>
        <field name="author_id" ref="module_5_qweb.andrzej_sapkowski_id"/>
    </record>

    <record id="the_last_wish_id" model="library.book">
        <field name="name">The Last Wish</field>
        <field name="book_description">
            The Last Wish (Polish: Ostatnie życzenie) is the second
            published (in Polish) of the two collections of short
            stories (the other being Sword of Destiny) preceding the
            main Witcher Saga, written by Polish fantasy writer Andrzej
            Sapkowski. The first Polish edition was published in 1993
            and the first English edition was first published on the 7th
            of June 2007. The book has also been translated into
            several other languages.
        </field>
        <field name="author_id" ref="module_5_qweb.andrzej_sapkowski_id"/>
    </record>

    <record id="blood_of_elves_id" model="library.book">
        <field name="name">Blood of Elves</field>
        <field name="book_description">
            Blood of Elves (Polish: Krew elfów) is the first novel in the
            Witcher Saga written by the Polish fantasy writer Andrzej
            Sapkowski, first published in Poland in 1994. It is a sequel
            to the Witcher short stories collected in the books The Last
            Wish (Ostatnie życzenie) and Sword of Destiny (Miecz
            przeznaczenia) and is followed by Time of Contempt (Czas
            pogardy). The book won the Janusz A. Zajdel Award in 1994
            and the David Gemmell Legend Award in 2009. An English
            translation was published in the United Kingdom in 2008
            (Gollancz) and in the United States in 2009 (Orbit).
        </field>
        <field name="author_id" ref="module_5_qweb.andrzej_sapkowski_id"/>
    </record>

    <record id="the_silmarillion_id" model="library.book">
        <field name="name">The Silmarillion</field>
        <field name="book_description">
            The Silmarillion is a collection of
            mythopoeic stories by the English writer J. R. R. Tolkien, edited
            and published posthumously by his son Christopher Tolkien in 1977
            with assistance from the fantasy author Guy Gavriel Kay.The
            Silmarillion tells of Eä, a fictional universe that includes the
            Blessed Realm of Valinor, the once-great region of Beleriand, the
            sunken island of Númenor, and the continent of Middle-earth, where
            Tolkien's most popular works — The Hobbit and The Lord of the Rings
            — are set. After the success of The Hobbit, Tolkien's publisher
            Stanley Unwin requested a sequel, and Tolkien offered a draft of
            the stories that would later become The Silmarillion. Unwin
            rejected this proposal, calling the draft obscure and "too Celtic",
            so Tolkien began working on a new story that eventually became The
            Lord of the Rings.
        </field>
        <field name="author_id" ref="module_5_qweb.tolkien_id"/>
    </record>

    <record id="lord_of_the_rings_id" model="library.book">
        <field name="name">The Lord of the Rings</field>
        <field name="book_description">
            The Lord of the Rings is an epic[1] high-fantasy novel[a] by
            English author and scholar J. R. R. Tolkien. Set in Middle-earth,
            intended to be Earth at some distant time in the past, the story
            began as a sequel to Tolkien's 1937 children's book The Hobbit, but
            eventually developed into a much larger work. Written in stages
            between 1937 and 1949, The Lord of the Rings is one of the
            best-selling books ever written, with over 150 million copies sold.
        </field>
        <field name="author_id" ref="module_5_qweb.tolkien_id"/>
    </record>

    <record id="hobbit_id" model="library.book">
        <field name="name">The Hobbit</field>
        <field name="book_description">
            The Hobbit, or There and Back Again is a children's fantasy novel
            by English author J. R. R. Tolkien. It was published in 1937 to
            wide critical acclaim, being nominated for the Carnegie Medal and
            awarded a prize from the New York Herald Tribune for best juvenile
            fiction. The book remains popular and is recognized as a classic in
            children's literature.
            The Hobbit is set within Tolkien's fictional universe and follows
            the quest of home-loving Bilbo Baggins, the titular hobbit, to win
            a share of the treasure guarded by a dragon named Smaug. Bilbo's
            journey takes him from his light-hearted, rural surroundings into
            more sinister territory.
        </field>
        <field name="author_id" ref="module_5_qweb.tolkien_id"/>
    </record>
</odoo>
